akrabat.com 2019-01-10

# Privacy policy – Rob Allen's DevNotes

I am Rob Allen and I operate this website (akrabat.com). This page is to inform you of my policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information received from users of the site. I only use your personal information for providing and improving this website. By using this website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### Information collection and use

I may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include your name and email address, which for example I ask for when you are submitting a comment. This is used to allow you to bypass moderation and have your comments appear directly on the website.

### Log data

I save the information that your browser sends whenever you visit this website (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s IP address, browser type, browser version, the pages of this website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

As an anti-spam measure, you have always been required to supply a name and email address in order to comment. Optionally, you may supply a website. If you comment on this website, then this information is stored, associated with that comment. If you wish to have that information removed, contact me. This may also end up with me removing your comment(s), though I will always try to preserve them.

This site uses Akismet to reduce spam. This is Akismet’s [privacy policy](https://akismet.com/privacy/) that explains how your comment data is processed.

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. This website also uses cookies to collect information for Google Analytics and to allow it to rememeber your name, email and website when you comment (should you choose to). You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.I f you do not accept cookies the remember your details when commenting feature will not be available.

### Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact me at [rob@akrabat.com](mailto:rob@akrabat.com%22).
